export const quiz = {
  totalQuestions: 20,
  questions: [
    {
      id: 1,
      question: 'What type of destination are you dreaming of?',
      answers: ['Beach', 'Mountains', 'City', 'Countryside', 'Island', 'Historical'],
    },
    {
      id: 2,
      question: 'What sort of weather are you looking for?',
      answers: ['Warm and sunny weather', 'Cool and breezy weather', 'Cold and snowy weather', 'No Preference of weather'],
    },
    {
      id: 3,
      question: 'How active would you like your getaway to be?',
      answers: ['Relaxing', 'Moderate Activity', 'Lots of Activities'],
    },
    {
      id: 4,
      question: 'Are cultural experiences important to you when traveling?',
      answers: ['Cultural experiences are very important to me', 'Cultural experiences are somewhat important to me', 'Cultural experiences are not important to me'],
    },
    {
      id: 5,
      question: 'What type of cuisine do you want to explore?',
      answers: ['Seafood', 'Desserts', 'Vegetarian/Vegan Options', 'Pastries', 'Street food', 'All kinds of food', 'No Preference of food'],
    },
    {
      id: 6,
      question: 'Whatâ€™s your preferred accommodation style?',
      answers: ['Hotel', 'BnB', 'Hostel'],
    },
    {
      id: 7,
      question: 'Who will you be traveling with?',
      answers: ['Solo', 'Partner', 'Family', 'Friends', 'Group Tour'],
    },
    {
      id: 8,
      question: 'What is your budget for this trip?',
      answers: ['$500 to $1,000', '$1,000 to $1,500', '$1,500 to $2,000', '$2,000 to $2,500', '$2,500 to $3,000', 'No limit of budget'],
    },
    {
      id: 9,
      question: 'How long would you like your getaway to be?',
      answers: ['Weekend', 'Three-five days', 'One week', 'Two weeks', 'Extended stay'],
    },
    {
      id: 10,
      question: 'Do you have a specific season in mind for your trip?',
      answers: ['Spring', 'Summer', 'Autumn', 'Winter', 'No Preference of season'],
    },
    {
      id: 11,
      question: 'What kind of activities do you enjoy?',
      answers: ['Adventure Sports', 'Cultural Events', 'Nature Walks', 'Shopping', 'Food Tours', 'Relaxing Spa Treatments'],
    },
    {
      id: 12,
      question: 'How important is safety to you when choosing a destination?',
      answers: ['Safety is my top priority', 'I consider safety but it is not a deciding factor', 'Safety is not a concern for me'],
    },
    {
      id: 13,
      question: 'Do you prefer popular tourist destinations or off-the-beaten-path locations?',
      answers: ['Popular Tourist Destinations', 'Off-the-beaten-path Locations', 'No Preference of location type'],
    },
    {
      id: 14,
      question: 'What mode of transportation do you prefer for traveling?',
      answers: ['Travel via airplane', 'Travel via train', 'Travel via car', 'Travel via bus', 'Travel via boat', 'No Preference of travel method'],
    },
    {
      id: 15,
      question: 'Do you prefer to plan your own itinerary or join a guided tour?',
      answers: ['Plan My Own Itinerary', 'Join a Guided Tour'],
    },
    {
      id: 16,
      question: 'What type of nightlife do you prefer?',
      answers: ['Vibrant nightlife with clubs and bars', 'Calm evenings with fine dining', 'No Preference of nightlife'],
    },
    {
      id: 17,
      question: 'Are you interested in outdoor adventures?',
      answers: ['Yes, I love outdoor adventures', 'I enjoy some outdoor activities', 'Not interested in outdoor activities'],
    },
    {
      id: 18,
      question: 'Do you prefer urban or rural environments?',
      answers: ['Urban environments with bustling streets', 'Rural environments with natural beauty', 'No Preference of environment'],
    },
    {
      id: 19,
      question: 'What is your preferred method of relaxation?',
      answers: ['Yoga and Meditation', 'Beach lounging', 'Spa treatments', 'Reading and Quiet Time', 'No Preference', 'Not interested in relaxation'],
    },
    {
      id: 20,
      question: 'Do you prefer destinations with a rich history or modern attractions?',
      answers: ['Rich History', 'Modern Attractions', 'I like Both Modern Attractions and Rich History'],
    },
  ]
};
